(This story is entirely fictional)
(Xu Meng)
Hey.
Xu Meng.
Custom-made just for you.
It's expensive.
(Based on Doctor Qin: Executer)
Mr. Zhang really likes it.
Look. How pretty.
You better not disappoint him.
Sir,
I don't wanna wear this.
What... what did you just say?
I... I don't want to.
Here, take it.
Here.
Say that again.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Mr. Zhang is waiting
to see you dance the starlight dance.
Hurry up!
Hands down.
Meng!
Meng.
Stay alive.
Surviving matters more than anything.
I'll definitely gather evidence
and make them pay.
I will.
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 10=
Meng.
Su wants you.
What are you two whispering about
that I can't hear?
Xiaoxue isn't feeling well.
I'm taking her
to the guest room to rest.
You do look a bit pale.
You're not having low blood sugar,
are you?
Should I go get you some juice?
No need.
The guest rooms have everything.
I'll take care of her.
You go entertain the guests.
Okay.
Get some good rest.
I'll call you two when I cut the cake.
You two can't miss me cutting the cake.
Xiaoya, happy birthday!
Let's take a photo together?
Sure.
Come on.
Come take a photo.
Coming.
Let's put our star in the center.
(Cheese.)
Jin Xiaoxue.
Mr. Wang really likes you.
He's especially happy
knowing you're here.
Come on!
Give Mr. Wang some entertainment.
Mr. Wang.
She really isn't feeling well.
How about I dance instead?
Who do you think you are?
Get lost.
Out.
♪Shadows roll over the girl's wall♪
♪The sunset is nailed to the tombstone♪
♪They say a cat has nine lives♪
♪Guess how many lives
I've lived through♪
♪The fluorescent powder
tears the scars open♪
♪Fresh blood feeds the crocodiles♪
♪They stroll down the hallway
with smirks♪
♪When the prey breaks free,
the hunter masks up and runs♪
♪Don't ask which hand
I settle scores with♪
Who... who's there?
Mr. Wang, you look good on camera.
Do you remember
what happened eight years ago?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Do you want me to post the video online,
or do you want to die
just like Zhang Xiaodong?
Mr. Wang.
You've got a son and a daughter.
Happy life.
What exactly do you want?
Do you think
they know what kind of man their dad is?
Come here.
It's you.
Sit down.
Mr. Wang,
you know what?
‌You can't see the fluorescent liquid
on the clothes during the day.
At night,
your whole body glows.
Girls like this color.
I've tried it.
Do you think
boys would like it?
Do you like it?
Like it?
Answer me!
You...
Name your price.
Fill it up.
Hurry up!
Okay.
Zhou.
I'm in the Diamond Room.
Bring me
five hundred thousand dollars.
Five hundred thousand.
Make it fast.
Don't ask why!
Just get it here fast!
You have fifteen minutes!
That's it!
So pretty.
Don't cry.
You're not pretty when you cry.
All you do is cry!
Come in.
Mr. Wang, the money's here.
Get out.
What are you looking at?
Time's almost up.
Is that enough?
Good boy.
Oh, and Mr. Wang,
stop using this color.
It's ugly.
Mr. Dong.
Where's Han Liang?
He's out on a call.
Fill me in.
We thoroughly checked all the accounts
and funding records
of the Sun Education Fund
over the past ten years.
It looked flawless.
But after deeper investigation,
we found they focused mainly
on remote areas.
They've been screening and funding girls
from extremely poor families
with no one to rely on.
He specifically targeted girls
in hardship.
A total scumbag.
We found three victims
who are now adults
and have left the city.
They all found the courage
to confirm to us
that Zhang Xiaodong
and his core assistants
would send funded girls
to Fengshan Villas
under the pretext of verifying info,
distributing cash,
or conducting one-on-one interviews.
Then they'd threaten
to cancel their eligibility,
make their families repay the money,
or expose their poverty and privacy,
and sexually assault them.
And some victims were later
passed on by them,
under the guise of job referrals
or meeting important people,
to certain investors
or bosses with special needs.
This has become a shady industry.
Even more horrifying,
according to one victim,
Zhang Xiaodong has a habit
of keeping indecent videos.
And he files them by name
as a tool for long-term blackmail.
List all the victims' names.
Whether they're willing to
come forward now or not,
we need to let them know
the police station door
is always open to them.
Immediately apply to
fully freeze
the Sun Education Fund accounts.
Seal all materials.
And give the highest level of protection
to confirmed victims and witnesses.
This lead
will be the strongest evidence
to bring down Zhang Xiaodong.
Yes, sir!
What time do you get off?
(01:55)
Ten more minutes.
You haven't contacted me
in all these years.
Am I that hard to reach?
Not hard.
Then what do you mean
by suddenly showing up now?
You weren't there
when I needed you most.
Now I don't need you anymore!
Stop coming to find me!
Let's go.
Home?
Yeah.
Didn't you say you'd drive me home?
Do you remember?
Back in high school,
you bombed a mock exam once
and cried all night.
I remember.
That night,
I even wrote you a letter.
In the letter,
you said you probably wouldn't get
into Longfan University.
You told me not to let you affect me.
Told me not to ignore you once I got in.
Do you think
I was really dumb back then?
No.
I thought
it was cute.
If...
I mean, if.
If I hadn't
dropped out that year,
and we had both gotten
into Longfan University together,
what would it be like?
Maybe
you'd work part-time,
working at a convenience store till two,
and I'd pick you up after your shift.
Like now?
Are you working
at the convenience store again tonight?
Will you come pick me up?
Yeah.
If only it were real.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm home.
Keke.
Qin Ming.
Stop coming to find me.
♪Back then, you and I turned away♪
♪Silence swallowed the sound of crying♪
♪Then I heard your name♪
♪Like thunder hits my heart♪
♪The warmth I once kept hidden♪
♪Turned to dust♪
♪I love you,
but it's a love I'll never have♪
♪The wild wind swept away
all the warmth♪
♪I love you,
but it's a love I'll never have♪
♪When we meet again,
there's nothing but silence and tears♪
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪